I'm going to push you now, so let's do the pushing together.
Do you dislike pushy women?
I absolutely hate them.
I hate them.
By someone you like.
I'm sorry. I can't do it.
I'm sorry.
Why?
You're having it done yourself? Mr. Suzuki.
Your teeth are cut. I hate it. I want to do another one.
me
me me me
If it's a word, I don't need it anymore.
I'm dreaming!
Well, look what we have here, ladies and gentlemen.
This is the staff of our beloved festival.
I'm sorry to say that we don't have time for this, but we're in the middle of starting the festival, and we haven't decided on the edition yet.
of high eyes!
was
I think that the StarPlaza Idol Festival has a lot of idols.
They're cute, so there's a lot of them.
Are you in? You want some?
Yes, I'm here!
You're here, aren't you? So many.
That's why you all want to meet them.
I want to meet him.
I want to meet him. I want to meet you.
So this time, I would like to do oshi-zumo.
Oshi-zumo?
Yes, I'm going to wrestle and if I win, I'll get a wish.
Yay!
Is there such a plan?
I'll stop with the menchures I'm always talking about.
I'm sorry about Harima.
I'm sorry about the Harima, but don't do it.
I can't say it in front of him,
I'm here, but this time it's Harima.
Huh?
You're here?
I was just here. Didn't you see him?
It's okay, it's the usual guy.
What's that?
I heard Harima's voice just now.
I made a mistake. That's HARIMA.
Someone tell me to get rid of Harima.
Someone should take care of Harima.
If this isn't there, I'm out.
No marshals? No?
No harima?
Maybe he's not here.
Maybe they're far away.
Jankake.
Jamake. Jankake.
Goo at first, poi at the end.
It's aiko, right?
Good night.
Then, I would like to practice until I can win the game with my partner, Kanako.
Yes, I will.
Thank you. Thank you very much.
Thank you.
But Aida is strong, you know. I'll do my best.
Pushing sumo.
Yes, Kiai.
He's left!
Can't you push, Kochan?
This is not yet.
I can afford it.
We won.
Aida, winner!
He was stronger than I thought.
Of course, I'm serious.
I'm serious, I'm serious.
What do you say? Please, we want you to make it happen.
What should we do?
We'll take all the money we have in the bank, please.
I don't even have a savings bag.
Also, please give me some of Harima's food.
I'm leaving yesterday, but I'll be fine.
Okay, okay.
You'll come to our rescue when we're in trouble with this YouTube.
Right to help?
Yes. Yes, sir.
They give you all the baths in Halima.
It's a bit of a slam,
If you need anything else, I'm here.
Yes, sir.
So, I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
So, that was our most recent guest, Harimakala.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Yes, so I got the cute little general idols right away.
These are the ones.
Yes, yes.
Yay.
Today, from today's memorial, we have Healin, Yulia, and Crown Popcan Milatee.
We are together.
I haven't explained the plan at all,
I'm going to ask you to push-wrestle with me now.
Why push wrestling?
Is it a showdown?
It's a real win. I may not be able to make the show because of a broken bone.
I'm here to buy.
Is that okay?
Go ahead.
Go ahead. Who's your favorite?
Julia, who looks like a winner.Julia, who looks like she can win.
Push sumo!
Yes, put your mind at ease.
Nakotan.
Can I protect your back?
My eyes are getting hot.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Are you strong?
I'm strong.
Hang in there.
Uri, I'm scared.
I'm scared.
My hand hurts.
I'm eating.
Hang in there.
You were so much weaker than before.
That's how strong you are.
Hang in there.
This way, this way.
That's great.
It hurts.
Hold on.
Okay, okay.
Draw.
How is this possible?
Oh, my God.
I'm scared. It's a hit or miss.
It's a hit and miss match.It was not a hit or miss, but it was the opposite.
It might have been a good fit.
Yes.
Pushing sumo!
Shikkyo!
Nakotan.
Eh, wasn't this just a little weak when you were pushing earlier?
Yay!
I got myself crushed.
I'm strong!
I won!
Strong, strong, strong!
Oh, that means I have to ask for a favor, right?
That's right.
Let's push! Ready, go! Nacotan!
Go, go, go!
Go for it!
I haven't done oshizumo in a while.
Oh!
Go for it!
He's really looking me in the eye.
Go for it! Go for it!
Oh, you like this?
I like the hair and the mouth.
Coo!
Cute!
Oh, no! Oh, no!
Go for it!
Come on, come on, come on, come on!
But I don't suppose you owe me anything?But did he owe you anything?
I think we might have lost what we owed.
Mirakey and Yuri won!
Yuzu was so eager to film on TikTok today.
Yuzu did something guerrilla on his personal account!
I won't tell you next time!
I won't tell you how to play.
You won't tell us?
Guerrilla.
Okay, okay.
Oh, a little bit.
It's okay.
It's like you're saying it out of the blue.
It's, uh, I'm not gonna do it.
You don't mind if I do?
I'll try.
Yes!
Wait a minute, it wasn't a bee game.
It was a draw, but they'll all play.
Am I right? Sorry.
You're right.
Move!
Are you having fun with that?
Oh! Yes, please!
Really?
I'm Rinko Nakayama, Gerris.
You're doing sumo wrestling?
Well, we're doing a guerrilla project right now.
We're doing a guerrilla project called "Oshi-Sumo".I've been working on a project to set up a sumo wrestling match with an old man.
It's very interesting!
But, I've never seen so many oshi-zumos...
Oh no, you can probably tell from what I've been doing...
I can't speak at all.
Yuu is the senior idol that I respect the most in the idol world.
He's so loud to everyone else.
In front of Rita-san, I can't speak at all.
I was watching her talking to Rita-san.
I tried to talk to her.
She doesn't say anything.
It's like, "Oh, no, I'm not talking!
I'm still in the mood for sumo wrestling!
He's so strong!
Yuu definitely wants to win!
Wow!
Oh, no! Is this overtime?
He's pushing his senpai down so hard. Isn't this an overtime?
- Amazing! I don't care if we lose or not, I just want to win.
- If you could do me one favor...
When I saw Stub Rider today, I wanted to film her on TikTok.
I'm going to ask you if I can sing our song without teaching you the choreography. I'll ask them.
- What? What are you going to say? What? What? Something like that.
You can ask either one at random. Just dance at random.
- Shall we go?
- You're swinging around all of a sudden.
- Thank you very much. It was a lot of fun.
- First time as a senior?
- That's great. Thank you very much. - That's great. Thank you very much.
- Thank you very much.
- Thank you very much. - Ivy Simcoe.
- Yes!
- I'm so glad you're here.
- I'm glad you're here. - Get ready to cut your teeth.
- Mantomaru!
- The one that went in.
- Yes, sir. And, by the way, here's our senior.
- Jimmy, can I get the camera...
- Use the camera.
- Oh, this one right here is good.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
- Camera over here.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on.
- Okay.